<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>API on DevOps | AWS | GCP | Golang | Python </title>
    <link>/tags/api/</link>
    <description>Recent content in API on DevOps | AWS | GCP | Golang | Python </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/api/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2019nCov-API [新冠疫情爬虫数据接口]</title>
      <link>/posts/2019ncov-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2019ncov-api/</guid>
      <description>The beginning of the year of rat is quite difficult for most Chinese people since the coronavirus outbreak. I have been checking the news about the progress of this outbreak. One day I watched the interview of a Chinese health official. She mentioned that there was one patient who has no idea that he has met anyone from Wuhan,the center of the outbreak. However, they used big data and found 3 people from Wuhan that have been in contact with him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Payment Gateway | Go | Stripe | Vault</title>
      <link>/posts/go-payment-gateway-with-stripe-and-vault/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/go-payment-gateway-with-stripe-and-vault/</guid>
      <description>In my previous posts, I have talked about how to build your own Google NLP API. You are a smart developer and you got a great idea 💡. You build an amazing API with useful functions. The only thing you are missing is a validated business case. I think the eaiset way to prove the use case is to put it in the market and see whether or not people are willing to pay for it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go NLP API | Build Your Own </title>
      <link>/posts/go-nlp-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/go-nlp-api/</guid>
      <description>In my previous posts, I have talked about building a small backend server to handle HTTP POST request. We also have tried out the Google NLP and we dived into the topic of NLTK. Well, now we know how to create a Go function to handle HTTP request and we understand the idea of Natural language Processing. Why not building your own Google NLP API?
Let&amp;rsquo;s now look at the key functions // Now we need to create a function to parse and tag all the data // There is a pre-built lib you can use - &amp;#34;gopkg.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>